# **Catherine Tang**

Taipei-Keelung Metropolitan area



cathytang912@gmail.com



0909448484



linkedin.com/in/catherine-tang912

# **Summary**

An experienced, disciplined and highly-motivated Configuration Business Analyst who has worked on a wide range of projects in the healthcare sector. An accomplished and fluent communicator with strong research, planning, problem-solving, leadership and decision-making skills. Highly accomplished with business analysis, software configuration, software testing and reporting.

# **Experience**

# **Business Analyst**

Innova Solutions

Mar 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months +)

Assisted in configuration of healthcare applications based on the client's business requirements.

Provided claims support - reviewing, researching, investigating and auditing claims.

Interpreted requests to develop configuration requirements and obtained approval from business owners.

Executed assigned configuration tasks as planned within deadlines.

Provided system configuration support based on business research needs.

Analyzed and resolved configuration issues in a timely manner.

Applications: Amysis, DST Provider Pricing and Golden.

# Business Analyst

#### Centene Corporation

Mar 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months +)

Delivered projects related to the development and configuration of new business, provider contracts, claims editing, reference data and their enhancements including claims configuration improvements, compliance and systems enhancements.

Provided support to the claims configuration process in addition to providing claims triage and configuration troubleshooting.

Ensured that business requirements for claims configuration change requests are clearly understood, documented, communicated, tested, and delivered.

Experience with data analysis and query tools that utilize functions that include creating standardized reports, utilizing VLOOKUPs, pivot tables, filtering and formulas.

Experience utilizing analysis tools such as SQL, project tracking, testing and requirement tools.

Hands-on experience and knowledge of rules based table driven claims and eligibility administration systems.

Proficient in medical terminology, medical coding (CPT4, ICD9 or ICD10, and HCPCS), provider contract concepts and common claims processing/resolution practices.

# **Contract Implementation Analyst**

Innova Solutions

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021 (6 months)

Assisted with audits of provider setup within the provider information system to ensure accurate contract implementation and subsequent claims processing.

Ensured accurate contract implementation and subsequent claims processing through change request submissions and UAT testing.

Analyzed, updated, and wrote internal knowledge base guides such as job aides.

#### **Contract Implementation Analyst**

Centene Corporation

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021 (6 months)

Interpreted specific state benefits, provider contracts as well as additional business requirements and converting these terms to claims configuration set up parameters.

Translated high-level business requirements into functional requirements.



## Technical Documentation Manager

D-Link

Jul 2019 - Oct 2020 (1 year 4 months)

Managed a team of four writers

Modernized writing tools from Indesign and Illustrator to Robohelp for online asset creation

Created standardisation guidelines for the team to follow in order to create congruent, reusable assets Created workflows for asset requests

Analyzed gaps for improvement of assets and implemented procedures

Worked with the translation agency; reviewed and handled translation quotes and invoices, negotiated contracts and budget analyzes



#### **Technical Writer**

D-Link

Sep 2018 - Jul 2019 (11 months)

Created manuals/datasheets/quick installation guides using Adobe InDesign, Illustrator and Photoshop

Tested apps and edited UI Strings

Reviewed website content

Peer reviewed documentation

Wrote video scripts

Part of the Global Marketing Department



## Clinic and Theatre Nurse at North Shore Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery

North Shore Oral & Maxillofacial Surgeons

Apr 2017 - Aug 2018 (1 year 5 months)

Created the clinic workflow for digital data storage

Organized, developed presentations and edited material for lecture seminars

Coordinated marketing materials for the company (video editing, seminar promotion, website upgrade, social media account management etc)

Circulating and scrubbing in a theatre environment

Conducted pre operation admissions, post operation recovery, education and follow up appointments

Conducted radiology scans (OPG and CBCT)

Conducted Intraoral scans using TRIOS

Created audits for Medication Management, Sterilisation, Cleaning and Documentation in the facility

Researched and collated a manual for Infection Control and Sterilisation for the facility

Experience in undergoing DAA Group audits and writing policies and protocols

Infection Control Nurse

Underwent Health and Safety training and formulated the workplace policy



### Theatre Nurse and Inventory Maintenance

#### Eye Institute

Jun 2015 - May 2017 (2 years)

Assisted in editing policies and procedures

Designed and created documentation to streamline paperwork

Circulating in a theater environment

Preparation of surgical instruments in a sterile field

Informing patients of post-operation care and medications

Preparing documents and medications for patients in the pre-operative stage

Examining and analyzing policies and conducting audits

Working in an iLASIK and ophthalmology surgical theatre

Ordering stock and maintaining inventory levels, drug supply management

#### novo Retail Manager

## Novo Shoes Group PTY LTD

2014 - Jun 2015 (1 year 6 months)

Responsible for stock management and keeping records of stock availability

Responsible for the organization of the stock room

Delegated tasks and trained staff, prepared daily tasks for staff to complete in advance

Rostering duties

Banked daily intakes and sorted out differences in banking

Maintained a high standard of display and visual merchandising and ensured the store was well presented

Was in constant communication with the Area Manager about the operations in store and completed weekly reports

#### **NOVO** Sales Assistant

#### Novo Shoes Group PTY LTD

Nov 2011 - 2014 (3 years 2 months)

Exceeded sales targets and customer services standards

Assisted customers with their purchases and special orders

Transferred stock in and out of store

Used modern computerized equipment and specialist retailing software

Processed customer transactions and maintained cash drawer

Maintained an expert phone manner with customers and other stores



### Teaching Assistant

ActiveKids

2010 - 2011 (2 years)

Setting up classrooms

Planning activities Interacting with elementary school age children Assisting the teacher in conducting classes

## **Education**

**AUT** Auckland University of Technology

Bachelor of Health Science (Nursing), Nursing 2011 - 2014

Australian International School Hong Kong

High School Certificate 2004 - 2010

## **Licenses & Certifications**

- Advanced Cardiac Life Support Level 5 Emcare Issued May 2016 Expires May 2018
- Acrysof IOL Loading In-Service Alcon
- Verion Image Guided System Digital Marker for Microscope Alcon
- The Centurion Vision System Alcon
- Certified Medical Reimbursement Specialist (CMRS) American Medical Billing Association (AMBA)

#### **Skills**

Information Technology • Healthcare • SQL • Amisys • Technical Documentation • Nursing • Retail • Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS) • Social Media • Video Editing